Guide to the Brotherhood of Railway, Airline, and Steamship Clerks, Freight Handlers, Express, and Station Employees: 1915-1985
Brotherhood of Railway, Airline, and Steamship Clerks, Freight Handlers, Express, and Station Employees
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives, Cornell University Library
Brotherhood of Railway, Airline, and Steamship Clerks, Freight Handlers, Express, and Station Employees: 1915-1985
5488 B
Brotherhood of Railway, Airline, and Steamship Clerks, Freight Handlers, Express, and Station Employees.
669 linear feet.
Correspondence, Rule books, Agreements, etc.
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives, Cornell University Library
SUBJECTS
Names:
Brotherhood of Railway, Airline, and Steamship Clerks, Freight Handlers, Express, and Station Employees.
Subjects:
Railroads--Employees--Labor unions--United States--Sources.
INFORMATION FOR USERS
Access Restrictions:
Restricted. Please contact the Kheel Center Reference Archivist for access information.
COLLECTION ARRANGEMENT
This forms a portion of collection #5488 B. The guide to the entire collection is available here.
Series LXXXIII is arranged in 17 sub-series by Union file number.
CONTAINER LIST
- Series LXXXIII. BUS AND TRUCK TRANSPORTAION
  - Sub-Series 431-0. Bus and Truck Transportation. General
    - General, 1955 (Box 596b, Folder 10)
      January-April 1955.
    - General, 1954 (Box 596b, Folder 11)
      September-December 1954.
    - General, 1954 (Box 597a, Folder 1)
      April-August 1954.
    - General, 1953-1954 (Box 597a, Folder 2)
      April 1953-March 1954.
    - General, 1952-1953 (Box 597a, Folder 3)
      December 1952-March 1953.
    - General, 1952 (Box 597a, Folder 4)
      April-December 1952.
    - General, 1951-1952 (Box 597a, Folder 5)
      June 8, 1951-March 1952.
    - General, 1951 (Box 597a, Folder 6)
      March 1951-June 7, 1951.
    - General, 1950-1951 (Box 597a, Folder 7)
      October 5,1950-February 1951.
    - United States Bureau of the Census. "Motor Trucking for Hire", 1937 (Box 597b, Folder 1)
      1937 May
    - Association of American Railroads. "State Regulations of Motor Vehicles, Passenger and Property Carriers", 1935 (Box 597b, Folder 2)
      1935 November 15
    - Motor Carrier Bulletin Supplements, 1937 (Box 597b, Folder 3)
    - Association of American Railroads. "State Regulations of Motor Vehicles, Passenger and Property Carriers", 1936 (Box 597b, Folder 4)
      1936 January 1
    - Association of American Railroads. "State Regulations of Motor Vehicles, Passenger and Property Carriers", 1935 (Box 597b, Folder 5-6)
      1935 January 1
    - General, 1950 (Box 597b, Folder 7)
      April 1950-October 4, 1950.
    - General, 1950 (Box 597b, Folder 8)
      January-March 1950.
    - General, 1938-1949 (Box 597b, Folder 9)
      November 1938-49.
    - General, 1934 (Box 598a, Folder 1)
    - General, 1933 (Box 598a, Folder 2)
    - General, 1930 (Box 598a, Folder 3)
    - General, 1930-1932 (Box 598a, Folder 4)
    - General, 1935-1938 (Box 598a, Folder 5)
      1935-October 1938.
    - Applications for Acquisition, Control or Merger, 1936-1937 (Box 598a, Folder 6)
    - United States Bureau of the Census. "Motor Trucking for Hire", 1937 (Box 598a, Folder 7)
    - Interstate Commerce Commission Bureau of Statistics. "Investment of Steam Railways in Highway Motor Vehicle Enterprises", 1936 (Box 598a, Folder 8)
      1936 October
    - General, 1932 (Box 598a, Folder 9)
    - Laws and Bills, 1932-1933 (Box 598a, Folder 10)
    - General, 1930 (Box 598a, Folder 11)
    - General, 1931-1932 (Box 598a, Folder 12)
    - General, 1931 (Box 598a, Folder 13)
  - Sub-Series 431-1. Bus and Truck Transportation. Missouri-Kansas-Texas Lines
    - General, 1930 (Box 598a, Folder 14)
  - Sub-Series 431-2. Bus and Truck Transportation. Missouri Pacific Railroad
    - General, 1931 (Box 598a, Folder 15)
    - General, 1930 (Box 598a, Folder 16)
  - Sub-Series 431-3. Bus and Truck Transportation. Central Vermont Railroad
    - General, 1930 (Box 598a, Folder 17)
  - Sub-Series 431-4. Bus and Truck Transportation. Seaboard Air Line Railway
    - General, 1930 (Box 598a, Folder 18-19)
  - Sub-Series 431-5. Bus and Truck Transportation. Southern Pacific Railway
    - General, 1931 (Box 598a, Folder 20)
    - General, 1930 (Box 598a, Folder 21)
    - General, 1936 (Box 598a, Folder 22)
  - Sub-Series 431-6. Bus and Truck Transportation. New Orleans, Louisiana
    - General, 1930 (Box 598a, Folder 23-24)
  - Sub-Series 431-7. Bus and Truck Transportation. Kansas City Terminal
    - General, 1931 (Box 598a, Folder 25)
  - Sub-Series 431-8. Bus and Truck Transportation. Chicago, Burlington and Quincy Railroad
    - General, 1931 (Box 598a, Folder 26)
    - General, 1936 (Box 598a, Folder 27)
    - General, 1932 (Box 598a, Folder 28)
  - Sub-Series 431-9. Bus and Truck Transportation. Railway Express Agency
    - General, 1931 (Box 598a, Folder 29)
    - General, 1932 (Box 598a, Folder 30)
  - Sub-Series 431-11. Bus and Truck Transportation. Great Northern Railway Company
    - General, 1932 (Box 598a, Folder 31)
  - Sub-Series 431-12. Bus and Truck Transportation. Milwaukee Railroad
    - General, 1932 (Box 598a, Folder 32)
  - Sub-Series 431-13. Bus and Truck Transportation. Illinois Central Railroad
    - General, 1933 (Box 598a, Folder 33)
  - Sub-Series 431-14. Bus and Truck Transportation. Texas and Pacific Railway
    - General, 1936-1938 (Box 598a, Folder 34)
  - Sub-Series 431-15. Bus and Truck Transportation. Santa Fe Railroad
    - General, 1936 (Box 598a, Folder 35)
  - Sub-Series 431-16. Bus and Truck Transportation. Gulf, Mobile and Northern Railroad
    - General, 1936 (Box 598a, Folder 36)
  - Sub-Series 431-17. Bus and Truck Transportation. Louisville and Nashville Railroad
    - General, 1936 (Box 598a, Folder 37)